So let's take a look at how he created the custom Word class.
دعونا نُلقي نظرة على كيفية إنشاء فئة كلمة مُخصصة.
A Word object should represent a single vocabulary word
يجب أن يمثل كائن الكلمة كلمة واحدة
that we want the user to learn.
والتي نريد أن يتعلمها المستخدم.
It should contain both the English and Miwok translations for the same word.
يجب أن يتضمن الترجمات باللغتين الإنجليزية وميوك لنفس الكلمة.
Now each of these translations can be stored as a string variable in
الآن، يمكن تخزين كل ترجمة كمتغير سلسلة حروف
the class.
في الفئة.
So to summarize the answer to the question what state should a Word object
واختصارًا لإجابة سؤال ما هي الحالة التي يجب أن يتضمنها كائن الكلمة
contain and what is the data type of each variable?
وما هو نوع البيانات الخاصة بكل متغير؟
Well the Word object should contain two string variables, one for the English
حسنًا، يجب أن يشمل كائن الكلمة متغيرين لسلسلة الحروف، واحد للترجمة
translation of the word, and one for the Miwok translation of the same word.
باللغة الإنجليزية للكلمة، وواحد للترجمة بلغة ميوك لنفس الكلمة.
Now this is what it looks like in a diagram.
هذا هو الشكل في رسم تخطيطي.
For the word object,
لكائن الكلمة،
we have an English translation and a Miwok text translation.
لدينا ترجمة باللغة الإنجليزية وترجمة نصية بلغة ميوك.
Since we know that this course is being utilized by students
بما أننا نعرف أن هذه الدورة ستكون لطلاب
who don't necessarily speak English as a primary language.
لا يتحدثون بالضرورة اللغة الإنجليزية كلغة أساسية.
We don't want to call the variable English translation.
لا نود أن نسمي المتغير ترجمة إنجليزية.
So instead we chose the term defaultTranslation
ولهذا، اخترنا مصطلح الترجمة الافتراضية
to represent the translation that is your primary language.
لتمثل الترجمة التي تكون هي لغتك الأساسية.
So to answer the question, what methods should we have?
للإجابة على سؤال، ما هي الوظائف التي يجب أن تكون لدينا؟
We should have a method to get the English translation and
يجب أن يكون لدينا وظيفة للحصول على الترجمة الإنجليزية
a method to get the Miwok translation.
ووظيفة للحصول على ترجمة لغة ميوك.
And here's what that looks like visually.
وهذا هو الشكل المرئي لتلك الوظائف.
So for the methods, this might have been a tricky one.
بالنسبة للوظائف، قد يكون الأمر معقد بعض الشيء.
Our Word class is the container that holds two variables.
تحتوي فئة الكلمات على متغيرين.
There's no complex logic to abstract away in the Word class.
لا يوجد منطق معقد لمعرفة الطريقة في فئة الكلمات.
We're just going to expose two methods in which some outside color can retrieve
سنقوم فقط بعرض الطريقتين حيث يستطيع لون خارجي استعادة
the English and Miwok translations.
الترجمات باللغتين الإنجليزية وميوك.
And again, instead of calling the methods getEnglishTranslation,
مرة أخرى، بدلًا من تسمية الوظيفة الحصول على الترجمة الإنجليزية،
we decided here to use getDefaultTranslation.
قررنا أن نستخدم الحصول على الترجمة الافتراضية.